Curriculum Vitae

Personal

Name Volodymyr Kurdiukov

Phone number +380937627275

Email volodymyr.kurdiukov@gmail.com

Website https://volodymyrkurdiukov.github.io/CV/dist/index.html

LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/volodymyrkurdiukov/

Resume objective

Freelancer. Junior front-end developer. Primary obligations: Contact the client, and discuss all terms, requirements, and responsibilities. Identification of all customer needs and requirements.

I am making suggestions and corrections from me as a specialist.

Completion of the project and subsequent transfer of all materials to the customer.

I have done several projects on freelance for customers, from simple landing pages to multi-page sites, and the customers were satisfied.

Skills

- Java Script (basic), jQuery(basic), HTML5, CSS, SCSS, SASS, BOOTSTRAP, Git, GitHub
- Adobe Photoshop, Figma, Zeplin
- Cross Browser & Device Compatibility, Responsive Design

Work experience

Dec 2022 - Jan 2023

Front-End Developer

Freelance (self-employed), Worldwide

Development of adaptive and cross-browser landing site for the company's product.

Order from a regular customer. The design of the mobile version was fully developed, which helped to save money for the customer and not pay for the additional creation of the mobile version from the designer. The whole site is made based on Swiper. As a result, the client is ready to cooperate further.

Nov 2022 - Dec 2022

Front-End Developer

Freelance (self-employed), WorldWide

Development of an adaptive, cross-browser site for an online company specializing in selling bio-additives.

The order was from a regular customer. Full development of the mobile version of the site helped the customer save money without ordering additional designs of the mobile version from the designer. As a result, the customer is satisfied and ready to cooperate further.

Oct 2022 - Nov 2022

Front-End Developer

Freelance (self-employed), Worldwide

Development of an adaptive, cross-browser website for the cosmetology clinic.

The layout was made with pixel-perfect technology, strictly following the customer's requirements. I am adding SVG animation. Working with a demanding client, as a result, the client was satisfied with the treatment.

Sep 2022 - Oct 2022

Front-End Developer

Freelance (self-employed), Worldwide

Development of an adaptive, cross-browser site for an online company specializing in selling bio-additives.

Customizing the design to the customer's needs.

Fully responsive design.
It has improved the user interface.
I am adding different visual effects.
I am adding different types of graphics.
Support for layout after handover to the client.

Education and Qualifications

Sep 2022 - Present *Udemy, Coursera, Prometeus, FreeCodeCamp, etc., Worldwide*

Web Developer, Front-End Developer, React Developer

I finished courses in web development, received a certificate with an excellent grade

May 2014 - Nov 2015 Master

Kharkiv National Agrarian University named after V.V.Dokuchayev, Kharkiv, Kharkiv Obtained master's degree field of study "Agronomy" obtained qualification of agronomist-investigator

Languages

Russian

English • • • • •